Allahu Akbar (God is the Supreme) X 4
La Elaha Ella Allah (There is no other god besides God)
Alhamdu Lillah, We praise God
Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah
And I bear witness that there is no other god besides the One God.
This is a... this is a very important Khutba, so I am going to stall a little bit for the rest of the late ones to be here.
This Khutba is so important that you are definitely a very select group of people who are destined to be here at this time.
But before I say anything, were is Ahmad Boruni?
You are his wife!
Good for you. Good for you.
Ok just to stall, I'm going to share with you Edip's discovery of last Khutba.
Give a chance to the late ones to be here.
It is an awesome discovery.
And it tells us that the Contact Prayers, God prescribes Al-Fãtehah, Sura number 1,
no more and no less, for the Contact Prayer.
It confirms what we have been doing for a few years, that is reciting only Sura number 1.
The mathematical evidence that God gives us, gave us,
and Edip discovered last week, or gave us last week
has to do with the physical structure of Sura number 1 and also the literal composition.
The physical structure, just that some of you may have missed the miracle last time, so I'm repeating it.
The physical structure is that the Sura is number 1 and it has 7 verses:
1 2 3 4 5 6 & 7. This is the physical structure of the Sura and this number is a multiple of 19.
Just putting the number of the Sura and the verses next to each other.
Now, you know that the morning prayer is 2 units, the noon is 4, the afternoon is 4,
the sunset is 3 and the night is 4.
And this number is a multiple of 19.
Putting the number of units next to each other.
19, of course, is the number that God Himself picked.
When people tell you why 19? Tell them because God said so in Sura 74.
God said it is the number 19 that will prove that the Quran is not human-made.
74:25 says some people will say the Quran is man-made.
And 74:30, God says 19 will prove to you that it is not man-made.
and 74:35 says it is one of the greatest miracles.
So, this is... this proves also the sequence of the prayers:
Morning, Noon, Afternoon, Sunset, Night,
And it is a multiple of 19,
and it is universally recognized, worldwide. There are no differences.
Now, the literal composition of the Sura is confirmed by the fact that
instead of the verse number, we put the number of the letters.
So, you put the Sura number which is 1,
The first... the first verse as you know is 19 letters,
(1:1) بِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمٰنِ الرَّحِيْمِ
the second verse: (1:2) ٱلْحَمْدُ لِلَّهِ رَبِّ ٱلْعَـٰلَمِينَ is 17 letters
You put 17 instead of 2.
The third verse is 12.
(1:1) بِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمٰنِ الرَّحِيْمِ (1:2) ٱلْحَمْدُ لِلَّهِ رَبِّ ٱلْعَـٰلَمِين (1:3) ٱلرَّحْمَـٰنِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
(1:4) مَـٰلِكِ يَوْمِ ٱلدِّينِ is 11
right!
11 letters.
(1:5) اِیَّاكَ نَعْبُدُ وَ اِیَّاكَ نَسْتَعِیْنُ
about the most important expression in the Sura:
You alone we worship. You alone we ask for help is 19.
We put 19.
and (1:6) ٱهْدِنَا ٱلصِّرَٰطَ ٱلْمُسْتَقِيمَ is 18.
(1:7) صِرَٰطَ ٱلَّذِينَ أَنْعَمْتَ عَلَيْهِمْ غَيْرِ ٱلْمَغْضُوبِ عَلَيْهِمْ وَلَا ٱلضَّآلِّينَ is 43 letters.
And this number also is a multiple of 19.
So, there you have it. Physical evidence.
Just in passing, we just received the Aramco magazine,
-The Arabian oil company-
And on the front cover, they have the last two verses of Sura 9, Satan's verses.
The Satanic verses on the cover
and inside they had Al-Fãtehah, written in the colloquial Arabic, not in the Quranic Arabic
where there was three extra letters.
So, they are trying hard to destroy God's miracle, but it is not working.
It's too late. The cat is out of the bag.
So, I hope you appreciate this miracle now and it is very clear.
Now that Abdullah is here, it means everyone is here.
So, I'm going to start my Khutba now.
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
This is a very important Khutba in that God is revealing so much information.
I'm going to repeat the assertion that you are a select group of people. You are destined to be here at this time.
The information that God is sending to us puts us an eternity ahead of anyone else living on Earth today.
The subsequent generations will catch up with us.
But today, on the planet earth, we are an eternity ahead of the rest of the world.
The picture of why we are here is emerging very clearly now.
And there is a lot more to be known but this is the time that God wills to send this information to us.
It is relevant to our generation.
And what this additional information, you know most of it, but the additional information shows how bad the human being is,
and how fortunate we, in this Masjid, are.
These are the two things, the subject of this Khutba:
How bad the humans are
and how fortunate we are.
It was Satan's ego, E G O, remember this word.
that made him think that he can be a god besides God.
And this triggered a division in the Heavenly community.
Some creatures agreed with Satan.
And this constituted the Heavenly Feud that we see in Sura 38, 19 x 2, verse 69, the Heavenly Feud
or the Feud in the Heavenly Community.
The vast, vast, vast majority disagreed with Satan.
They stood on the side of God's absolute authority, and those are the angels.
They never questioned the fact that only God can be a god.
And their number is unknown to anybody. Only God knows.
Sura 74, verse 31.
It says no one knows the number of God's soldiers, the angels, except He.
Even the angels do not know what their population is.
So, don't be tricked by the fact that 150 billion creatures agreed with Satan.
Those are a very very small minority.
So, now we have a minority, the criminal element in the Heavenly society that's you and me and the jinns,
failing to make a stand on God's absolute authority.
God, the Most Merciful, offered this criminal element another opportunity to renounce their crime and to submit to God.
And the majority of these creatures, the vast vast vast majority took advantage of that opportunity,
which we see in Sura 33, verse 72
and those are the animals, the mountains, the stars, the trees
You remember in Sura 22, verse 18, God says do you not realize that the mountains, the trees, the animals prostrate to God and some people.
Remember that verse?
In Sura 55, verse 6, God says the stars and the trees prostrate.
What does this mean?
It's because they decided, they took advantage of that second opportunity to submit to God.
The horse is a submitter to God. He was one, the horse is one of those creatures.
They committed that initial blasphemy and took advantage of the second offer.
The horse is a perfect submitter.
He comes to you on four, you know like this,
ego, remember ego? The word ego.
The horse comes to you like this and says ride me.
And the horse will let a poor person ride him.
or a rich person. A child will lead the horse wherever the child wants.
The horse is a perfect submitter.
And this was the deal that the animals accepted to come here in a subservient, obedient function.
And in return for this obedience are redeemed to God's kingdom in the Hereafter.
That was the deal.
The dog wags his tail to the homeless.
You see a homeless person walking on the street, very poor
And he is taking along a dog with him and the dog loves him, wags his tail.
The president of the United States has dogs also and they wag their tails to the president.
Not because he is the president; they do not even know that they live in the White House.
They can live in the street with the homeless or in the White House and they are submitting, they wag their tails.
When God asked you and me do you want to go to the world?
God told us about the plan.
Do you want to participate in this plan as a horse?
The poor will ride you. The rich will ride you. A child will lead you.
And you and I said no way!
Me?! Go as a horse?!
Ego, remember?
This criminal element...
It is the ego that brought us here.
And it is the ego that stands, as an obstacle, between us and redemption.
There were so many of the creatures who decided to take advantage of the second offer,
that they could not all come here as animals. We'd be over crowded.
So, God made them stars and the stars prostrate. They go on the precise orbit.
The Sun rises and sets at exactly the same times.
Today, September 29, the Sun rises 6:16.
It's not 6:15 or 6:20. 6:16.
And next year, it's going to rise at 6:16.
If you watch the horizon at the east at 6:16, there comes the Sun disk; see it coming up, submitting.
It's going to set at 6:11, not 6:10.
And this is, this is eternal. This is eternal calendar.
The moon synchronized around the earth, following, following exactly the orbit.
Halley's comet comes every 76 years.
They wait for it and, sure enough, here it comes every 76 years.
It goes, God knows where, but 76 years, it comes back to the Solar system and we see it.
We refused. We are so bad.
The human being is so bad. This explains why all these people are oblivious to God.
And you can see that their ego is preventing them.
God says in 33:79,
That the human being was unjust, stupid
ظلوماً جهولاً
Ignorant. God calls it ignorant.
But I'm not as polite as the Quran. But it really is... this is the most fitting word.
When God told the horse you go as a horse and you'll be redeemed to God's kingdom. He said I'll take it. I'll take it.
And they come here and perform their functions.
And they go back.
Even our bodies are submitting.
Because the body is part of the earth.
The earth is submitting to God.
The body is a garment made of the earth,
just like this came out of the oil from the ground.
A garment.
And your heart. You cannot control your heart. It is out of your control.
Your peristalsis, the intestines, moving. They move like this.
They push the food all the way to your stomach until you digest it.
You don't control that. Miles and miles of your intestines are moving right now in a precise motion.
The lungs are breathing.
You do not control that.
Because the earth is submitting to God. Your body is part of the earth.
And you cannot control it.
But the human being is so bad.
If I draw a line of God's creatures in the Heavenly community, like this.
And Satan... Satan's ego told him that he can be a god besides God.
By the way this, this minor rebellion proves to us that God's creatures have a freedom of choice.
This is the usefulness or the purpose of this rebellion.
The humans say why did God create rebellious creatures?
And God takes this into consideration.
And this is why millions of people die before the age of 40 and are redeemed.
Obviously they deserved it, but they participated in this very important function.
The hardcore enemies of God will end up in hell.
And I love Ismail Barakat's expression yesterday
When we were talking about what you read in the perspective about changing the name of Muhammad, even their idol, to five letters, Muhamamad محممد.
Instead of محمد, just to oppose the miracle.
He said they are storming the gates of hell.
This is what he said. storming.
God builds fences around hell, and very strong gates and they're storming the gates of hell.
So, when Satan did this, the vast majority of God's creatures agreed,
but a small minority...
Can you see this back there?
This is the criminal element in the Heavenly community.
Now, if we expand this here.
When God offered the second opportunity for them to submit, the vast vast majority of them submitted.
And the real bad ones - we were just about this much -
That's you and me, the humans and jinns. We refused
because you know how many horses there are in the world, and how many mosquitos and cockroaches, Edip... and bees.
So, the vast majority took advantage of the second.
These are the real bad ones.
Me, go down as a horse?! No!
You know, this is ego. We thought we are smart enough to make the right decision.
See, God told us that if you make the right decision, you'll come back to the High Heaven, which is fantastic.
And this is the second part of my sentence how fortunate we are.
This is how bad, this is how bad the humans are.
TOOBOO ILLA ALLAH. Repent.
Alhamdu Lillah, Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
What you just did now, repent, means you said you're sorry for doing this.
We made a mistake, we want to be redeemed back to God's kingdom.
We don't wanna be exiled from God.
We were exiled because of our ego.
The reason, you and I refused to come here as a dog or a horse or a mosquito
was that we thought that we, oh, it's easy. It's a piece of cake. We're gonna... we'll choose God. We will not choose Satan.
My thought got interrupted here.
Yes, I want to mention that, since it is the ego that is preventing us, the obstacle between us and God's kingdom,
Kill your ego is one of the first commandments in the Quran.
Kill your ego.
2:54. Sura 2, verse 54. In the first 10 pages of the Quran, it says, Kill your ego.
And kill means dead.
You see how the horse is.
We are supposed to kill our ego, as far as God is concerned.
Killing the ego is not that somebody comes, slaps you in the face and you turn the other cheek. No.
You stand. In fact, God says the believers are not whims.
They stand up for their rights.
But as far as God is concerned, you must kill your ego.
Because I'm telling you the ego is what is preventing millions of people today from going to Heaven.
And what let some of us to drop out is when God willed that I announce my messengership.
The only reason they refuse is the ego
because God gave them so much evidence and gave them zero evidence against it.
We're still waiting for one reason, good or bad.
They can't come up with one. There is no reason
that say you are not God's messenger. There is no reason.
But it's the ego. And they can't come up and say it.
They can't say it's my ego that is... It is because of my ego I don't wanna recognize you as God's messenger.
And it seems to me now that this is part of the test. Not it is part of the test, but I mean it is a difficult test
that God puts us through in order to kill our ego.
He is one of us who claims to be God's messenger.
How are we gonna... And then God says obey God and obey the messenger in the Quran. How am I gonna do this?
He's just like me.
It's ego, our ego.
I actually sympathize with those people.
It took me 8 years to accept that.
And I don't wanna give myself a test. I have enough of my own.
but I do wanna ask myself if I were in their shoes, what will I do?
But it is definitely the ego and God is fair.
If they flunk, they deserve it.
It is strictly ego.
What is the reason? What is their reason?
You know they could have come with a reason saying God says Muhammad is the last messenger in the Quran. And this should be over, be finished.
But they don't come up with a reason like that because there is no such thing.
The Quran says Muhammad was the last prophet, a message, scripture-bearing messenger but he was not the last messenger.
The Quran makes it very clear.
I don't know, they could have come with a hundred reasons.
Edip: Chicago conference.
The messenger: Yeah. Things are brewing now. This may change their direction
But I think I said everything I wanted to say any way.
There is many more that we'll discuss tonight Insha Allah, and in the next months and years, Insha Allah.
We'll be discussing these.
God will send more information.
But the highlight is that I wanted to point out this how bad the human being is and how fortunate we are.
They established something called the counsel on the preservation of the finality of prophethood.
And this includes the top witch in the Muslim world:
The Pope of the Sunni Muslims, Sheikh Al-azhar, the head, the imam of the Ka'ba, the Mecca Masjid, the head of the Muslim world league
And they are holding a conference, an urgent conference in Chicago, October 7. It is two weeks from now.
It's called world conference on the finality of prophethood.
And they are trying to confuse the people. Remember the verse in Quran that says they distort the words out of context.
They are trying to confuse the people as far as the definition of prophet and messenger are concerned.
And since Edip brought this up, I'm gonna read the letters to you that I wrote to them.
This is their flyer.
And it says World Conference on Finality of the Prophethood and Significance of Hadith.
And they say, conference will start on Saturday October 7th. There is no Insha Allah.
You will not see the name of God in this sheet.
There is not a single word, God, on this sheet. There is no Quran on this sheet.
There is Hadith and there is a picture of prophet's mosque which he never saw.
Right here.
And it gives you the names, the Sheikh Al-azhar and so on.
And you know something, we will be there.
We'll be represented there. I'm gonna give them a lot of trouble.
Herbert Hill, you know him from Chicago. He was here for the conference.
He's taking his brother who used to be a Sunni and he's... he's being saved.
And maybe some other people, and they will go there and will ask some crucial questions.
Like what is the difference between Prophet and Messenger?
Tell me where in the Quran does it say, Muhammad is the last messenger?
Who is the messenger of the Covenant that is in 3:81? Et Cetera. Et Cetera.
We have 19 questions for them.
Oh, the letter that I wrote to them:
I sent it to each one of the top leaders and I said:
to these people from Rashad Khalifa regarding world conference on finality of the prophethood.
Dear brothers, As-Salamu Alaykum. No one is questioning the fact that Muhammad was the final prophet Nabi. Quran 33:40.
According to 3:81, 33:7 and 33:40, he was not the last messenger Rasool.
As Muslims, we are required to believe Almighty God when He so states in His Holy Book.
The Quranic assertions that Muhammad was the final prophet but not the final messenger,
are God's commandments to us through the prophet Muhammad.
I trust that you stand ready to obey God and His final prophet.
You will readily agree with me that those who refuse to accept these Quranic truth are no longer Muslims, Quran 3:81-85.
As God's Messenger of the Covenant, supported by overwhelming physical evidence,
it is my obligation to invite you to examine these Quranic truths.
and examine the evidence God has given me to present to you and to the world.
You are cordially invited to Masjid Tucson at any time you choose to discuss this matter and examine my evidence.
Thank you and may God bless you with His guidance and infinite mercy.
Forgive me for saying this your brother in Islam, Rashad Khalifa.
There has to be some diplomacy there.
Aqem Al-Salat.